<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.4//EN"
  "/usr/share/sgml/docbook/xml-dtd-4.3-1.0-25/docbookx.dtd">
 
<article>
  <articleinfo>
    <title>EPICS Canberra mca Support Module User Guide</title>

    <copyright>
      <year>2007</year>
      <holder>Copyright 2007 Diamond Light Source Limited</holder>
    </copyright>

  </articleinfo>

  <sect1>
    <title>Canberra 2016 Amplifier / Triple Channel Analyser</title>

    <para>Please consult <ulink
url="http://diamdocs2003.diamond.ac.uk/sites/default/TECHNICAL%20DIVISION%20(TEC
)/Controls%20and%20Interlocks%20CTRL/Supplier%20Documentation/Canberra/2016%
20Amplifier-TCA%20User%27s%20Manual.pdf">Canberra Industries  User Guide to the
Model
2016 Amplifier/TCA </ulink></para>
      <sect2>
      <title>EDM Screen</title>
        <mediaobject>
            <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="images/xxIcbTCA_edl.png" format="PNG"/>
            </imageobject>
            <textobject>
            <phrase>The EPICS edm screen for the TCA</phrase>
            </textobject>
            <caption>
            <para>The EPICS edm screen for the TCA.</para>
            </caption>
        </mediaobject>
        <sect3>
        <title>Output Polarity</title>
        <para>The input polarity of the amplifier. Options are Normal or
Inverted</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>ICR Threshold</title>
        <para>The Fast Discriminator circuit provides an Input Count Rate to
ratemeters and a front panel LED. It's output is also used in the Pile 
Up Rejection system. An event is deeemed to have occurred if a signal within
the Fast Discriminator exceeds a threshold. This threshold can be set manually
using a front panel adjustment or automatically. Options are Manual</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>Enable SCA's</title>
        <para>There are configurations involving multiple 2016 modules where
you may wish to disable the Single Channel Analyser outputs from all but 1.
Options are Yes or No.</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>Status Rate</title>
        <para>The period between re-reads of the module settings. Default
value is 10 seconds.</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>PUR Enable</title>
        <para>Enables the use of a Pile Up Rejector to reject events during
the time that a pile-up is deemed to have occurred based on the signal from
the Fast Discriminator. Options are Yes or No.</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>PUR Enable</title>
        <para>Enables the use of a Pile Up Rejector to reject events during
the time that a pile-up is deemed to have occurred based on the signal from
the Fast Discriminator, the SCA's ROI ( Single Channel Analyser's Region of
Interest) lower reference level (LLD) and upper reference level (ULD).
Options are Yes or No.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>PUR Amp</title>
        <para>This is another switch to enable the Pile Up Rejector. Options are
Yes or No.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>Select TCA</title>
        <para>There are configurations involving multiple 2016 modules where
you may wish to disable the Amplifier output from all but 1. Options are Yes
or No.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>Status</title>
        <para>Displays the status of the module. Possible values are Online,
Self-test error, Module reset or Can't commun.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>ROIs of SCAs Enable</title>
        <para>Allows you to control over whether input pulse discrimination
based on a region of interest is used to control the outputs of the SCA's.
Options are Enable or Disable.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>ROIs of SCAs Calibration</title>
        <para>Allows overall calibration of the region of interest used in
the input pulse discrimination. Range is 0.5 to 1.5.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>Gate</title>
        <para>There is 1 gate per SCA used to enable the SCA. Options are
Enable or Disable.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>PUR</title>
        <para>There is 1 PUR setting per SCA used to activate the Pile-Up
Rejector circuitry for that SCA. Options are Yes or No.
Enable or Disable.
</para>
        </sect3>
        <sect3>
        <title>Low & High </title>
        <para>There is 1 Low and 1 High setting per SCA. The FPGA within the
2016 uses these values to determine if an input pulse should cause a pulse
on the associated SCA. The values are in percentage of the overall range of
the signal into the comparator within the module. The range is 1 to 100%.
</para>
        </sect3>
      </sect2>
  </sect1>    
</article>